The Santa I work for is tiny and cute.
I'm delivering a bunch
of presents again this year!
Let's work hard, reindeer!
Right!
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho...
Looks heavy.
Santa!
If you don't mind...
Uh, Santa?
I know we're going to be really busy today,
but let's try not to overdo it.
We'll be efficient and avoid overtime.
Well...
Yes?
I wasn't reaching out... for a hug...
but rather offering to carry your packages...
I am so sorry!
Don't worry! Let's do a good job today!
Mistake or not, she gave me a hug.
Well, it's Christmas...
so it's probably fine, right?
Santa?
R-Right! On my way!
Happy, merry Christmas!
A... A dream?
Manager
Don't worry about the dream
Don't worry about the dream.
How did he know?!
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
Wow, look at all those people!
#06 I Can't Resist My Instincts!
Sorry to ask you to help me sell...
Not a problem! It's not like I was busy.
Besides, I helped you draw it,
so of course I'd help you sell it!
Helping me draw it...
That was...
Days Earlier
You look exhausted. Working on your manuscript?
Deadline's the day after tomorrow.
And all my friends who usually
help out are super busy, so...
That sounds rough.
What's all this?
You need some help?
M-Manager!
It's not work-related, so...
I'll do anything I can!
Still... there are certain technical
qualifications involved.
Hayakawa-san.
This is a template for in-store installations
that the manager drew before!
Wow!
What is this, a new game plus for you?
I haven't reincarnated, no.
Manager, can you hear me?
Loud and clear!
I'm gonna upload something to the cloud.
Let me know when you see it.
Got it!
In that case, could you start
with pages 16 to 22?
Roger!
Could you take a look
when I finish the first page?
Understood.
It might be an 18 plus BL book,
but that scene isn't too sexy...
I'm glad I was able to get help.
I'm really impressed, Hayakawa-san.
It's amazing that you can create something
so incredible from scratch.
Thank you...
I appreciate it, but considering it's 18 plus BL...
And with it being a derivative work,
it's not exactly from scratch!
I finished my first page!
Check it out!
O-Okay.
Wow!
But...
I accidentally asked him
to handle a sexy scene!
Gotta say, that was a lot of fun!
Our first project together.
Now that this 18 plus BL book is finished,
it's the product of our love!
That's not exactly wrong,
but could be interpreted in a weird way!
Here's hoping the product
of our love sells a lot!
Maybe that's what I should have
titled the book...
Chika-chan! It's been ages!
How've you been? It's been a while
since I've seen you IRL.
I'm pretty good!
It was last summer,
right, Haruna-chan?
And this is...?
Nice to meet you!
Your boyfriend!
No!
I told you!
I needed some help, and someone
from work was nice enough to offer!
So you work with him...
and he's your boyfriend!
Why would you assume that?!
Oh! On your bag there...
Isn't that Hime-chan from Kimihime-chan?
You know it?! That's impressive!
I just started watching it
after it was recommended to me!
By my girl here.
My girl
= Girlfriend
= Chummy
So he really is your boyfriend!
I keep telling you, no!
Well, everyone, have a good year!
The year's almost over...
Shinozaki Takuma
Well, we did exchange contact information...
The annual event is being held again this year,
and as you can see, there are
a ton of guests yet again.
I wonder who's calling so late?
How did you enjoy the event?
Uh, is this for TV?
Katase Shiori (Senpai)
Honestly, great! Her BL book
has been a huge success!
S-Senpai?!
Senpai's calling?!
Manager, come on!
Right... that's right!
We did trade contact info!
I'm such a lucky guy!
I mean...
Better answer.
Uh, hello, this is Shinozaki.
Sorry, I'm at my parents' house right now...
It's been kind of busy.
Is everything okay?
I'm sorry for calling so late.
No, it's totally fine!
What's up?
I just wanted to thank you
for everything this year.
Thank me?
Yeah.
You did a really great job over the last year.
Working with you helped me do better, too.
No! I feel like I was more
a nuisance than anything...
Y'know, when your senpai thanks you,
it's okay to think "Wow, I did a great job!"
Wow, I did a great job... then.
There you go! Well done.
Oh, wait, was that one last abuse
of authority before the year was over?
I'm hoping she'll continue to abuse
her authority in this way next year, too!
But...
I'm really glad you're my kohai, Shinozaki-san.
Me, too. I'm glad you're my senpai, Senpai...
I'm...
I wouldn't want anyone else...
for my senpai, Shiori-san.
Well, uh, here's to another year
working together!
R-Right, let's keep up the good work...
Manager
I sensed something
You should go to the Hatsumode
I sensed something.
You should go to the Hatsumode.
Manager?!
Hatsumode...
Visiting a shrine with Senpai...
Maybe I should invite her.
Li'l bro. You've got a girlfriend, don't you?
Shinozaki Yutaka
(Takuma's older sister)
Huh?
No, no, and where did that even come from?!
I don't!
There's no way you'd buy
that cute little getup on your own.
A-A senpai from work gave it to me.
A senpai from work...
Wh-What now?
She's a woman, isn't she?
W-Well, yeah...
Now, hold on! It's not like that!
I see... so at long last,
my little brother has found a woman.
Listen to me!
My Tiny Senpai. Meow!
Shinozaki-san invited me to Hatsumode.
I wonder what I should wear?
There's a senpai where I work...
Please adopt me
who is a tiny cat!
What happened, Senpai?!
What's going on here?!
Please adopt me
And it looks like you've been abandoned?
Meeeow! Mew mew!
Wh-Wh-What is happening?!
She's cute... too damn cute!
W-Will she get mad if I touch her...?
What is this?! Am I going to die?!
Killed by cuteness?!
M-Meow...
Cause
of death:
cuteness
Cause of death: cuteness.
"Please adopt me." I can't...
If I take Senpai home when she's this cute...
my heart won't be able to take it.
S-S-Senpai?!
I-I know you're cat, but you can't!
Some things are just
not appropriate, even for animals...
Meow...
I can't believe my first dream of
the new year was like something like that...
Manager
Don't worry about the dream
Don't worry about the dream.
Again?!
I woke up... and meow I'm a cat!
Wh-Wh-What's happened to meow?!
And this sign... did someone throw meow out?!
Huh?
An abandoned cat?
Sh-Shinozaki-san?!
I actually look like a cat to him, don't I?!
Will she get mad if I touch her?
My kohai from work...
I should be embarrassed...
to have him see meow like this...
M-My body...
It's... got this urge...
I-I don't think I can...
resist meow instincts!
Pet me! Pay attention to me!
For meow to be doing this...
I'm embarrassed,
but can't resist!
What is it? You want me to pet you?
There you go.
Shinozaki-san's big hands feel so nice...
Does it feel good when I touch you there?
Sh-Shinozaki-san! When you say it like that,
it sounds naughty to meow!
But...
it does feel good.
Which is why...
I'd want you to pet me...
when I'm not a cat.
Shinozaki-san...
That's one crazy dream
to start the new year with...
Manager
Don't mind the dream
Don't worry about the dream.
How did he know?!
I'm Shinozaki Yutaka, an office worker.
And my brother has been
acting weird since he got home.
I'm going out tomorrow.
Oh, really? With who?
Someone from work.
My bangs are getting long...
Maybe I should've gotten a haircut.
I'm positive.
He's absolutely got a woman!
Li'l bro. Time for a psychology test.
Where is this even coming from...?
You're walking down a road,
and you see three animals in front of you.
If you could give rubbies
to one of them, which one?
"Rubbies"?
A: A clever doggy.
B: A sexy female cougar.
These options are getting weird...
C: A cute little kitten.
The kitten... I guess.
I see. Then his woman must be the kitty type.
Now, how is this kitten behaving?
There's more?!
Fluffy
A: Fluffy.
Meow-meow-ey
B: Meow-meow-ey
Aren't these all typical for cats...?
Smiley
C: Smiley.
Can animal's smile?!
I guess... fluffy, meow-meow-ey, and smiley?
I see. Then my brother's girl is
like a fluffy, meow-meow-ey, smiley kitty...
In that case, I should check her out.
This fluffy, meow-meow-ey,
smiley kitty woman of his!
Senpai!
Shinozaki-san!
Happy New Year.
I'm looking forward to
working together this year.
S-So cute...
Happy New Year.
The feeling is mutual.
Shinozaki-san...
Senpai...
This is awkward, after that dream...
Looks like we're in for another sweet year!
What are you talking about, Manager?
I mean, come on!
Wh-What's that supposed to mean, Manager?
That's it... It must be.
My brother's woman.
Wh-Wh-What in the world?!
What even is that adorable, little thing?!
Her hair is so fluffy!
And she's meow-meow-ey and smiley...
Yes, quite fluffy indeed.
What are you even doing, Sis?!
I'm performing a background check, clearly.
Are you Shinozaki-san's big sister?
Indeed. Forgive me for startling you.
My name is Katase.
We work in the same department.
Your brother is always a ton of help.
Enough, already!
His sister never changes...
What do you mean?
She's always gone crazy
over small, cute things.
May I take her home with me?
Obviously not!
Shinozaki-kun's sister.
Who's this?
This is our department's manager.
Oh, Chika-chan's here, too.
It's a pleasure to meat you.
My brother's boss...
Katase-san and Shinozaki-kun
are such a great pair,
which is evident by how
excellently they work together.
Shinozaki-kun's thorough
but over-cautious approach
is an excellent match for Katase-san's
dynamic and supportive style.
On top of their contributions to the team,
they also help set
a positive tone in the office.
I'm curious, miss...
The name's Yutaka.
Yutaka-san.
Do you have any siblings
other than Shinozaki-kun?
It's just the two of us.
How do you feel about...
having a tiny, cute little sister?
Well, let's see...
Ideally, she'd be fluffy,
and meow-meow-ey, like this.
You realize... you'd get one
if your brother marries her.
Big sister!
Big... sister...
Yes!
Li'l bro!
So, when's the wedding?
Wha...
Go home!
You're both adults, so there shouldn't be
any problems in terms of age.
Did it not occur to you
there are other considerations?!
Get Married Beam!
There's no such beam!
You seriously haven't changed.
And you should
stop toying with them, Manager!
But come on!
I'm so sorry, Senpai...
My sister can be really rude.
It's okay...
It's good to see you two get along.
Is that what it looks like?
I'm not so sure.
We always tended to like the same things,
so we'd end up fighting over stuff.
You like the same things...
I... I see.
Does that mean, Shinozaki-san...
When it comes to me...
Er, well...
You two!
I get to give a speech at the wedding, right?
No, it's me, right?!
As the groom's sister, it's me!
I'm both the groom and
the bride's boss. It should be me!
Me!
It has to be me!
No, no, me!
Me! Me!
Hard to say whether they get along or not...
So, which one?!
Which one what?!
Come to think of it, does Yutaka-san
ever mess with you, Hayakawa-san?
Well, I'm not small or cute, after all.
You seem small and cute to me.
Manager... listen...
For favors at the ceremony,
we can give away these cute plates
with a print of Shiorin on them.
I'm "Shiorin" now...?
Wait, what about me?
No one cares.
Why not?!
The trend these days is to have people
pick from a catalog, anyway.
Don't encourage her, Manager!
Enough already!
Okay.
Come on, let's all head to the shrine together!
Sounds good. I wonder
if there'll be food stalls.
You want one of these?
No, I don't.
I sure hope so!
Wanna put the cat ears on?
No, I don't!
They're so cute, though...
Never!
Oh, cotton candy!
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar